db.questions.insertMany([{
Sports:{
	Easy:[
		{Question:"How many players per team are there in court in handball?",Answer: "7",choiceA: "6",choiceB: "7",choiceC: "8",choiceD: "9"},
		{Question:"How many squares are there in a chess board?",Answer: "64",choiceA: "48",choiceB: "56",choiceC: "64",choiceD: "72"},
		{Question:"What is the name given to the NFL final?",Answer: "Super Bowl",choiceA: "Super Bowl",choiceB: "World Cup",choiceC: "Wimbledon",choiceD: "The Masters"},
		{Question:"When did the FIFA World Cup take place in the USA?",Answer: "1994",choiceA: "1991",choiceB: "1992",choiceC: "1993",choiceD: "1994"},
		{Question:"",Answer: "",choiceA: "",choiceB: "",choiceC: "",choiceD: ""},
  ],
	Medium:[
		{Question:"The tiger Hodori was the mascot of which Olympic Games?",Answer: "Seoul 88 Olympic Games",choiceA: "Seoul 84 Olympic Games",choiceB: "Seoul 86 Olympic Games",choiceC: "Seoul 88 Olympic Games",choiceD: "Seoul 90 Olympic Games"},
		{Question:"Swords are used in which of the following martial arts?",Answer: "Ninjutsu",choiceA: "Ninjutsu",choiceB: "Chijutsu",choiceC: "Jujutsu",choiceD: "Chajutsu"},
		{Question:"What year were the first modern Olympics Games held?",Answer: "1896",choiceA: "1894",choiceB: "1896",choiceC: "1898",choiceD: "1900"},
		{Question:"What country is Taekwondo originally from?",Answer: "Korea",choiceA: "China",choiceB: "Japan",choiceC: "Thailand",choiceD: "Korea"},
		{Question:"Who won the Formula One World’s Driver Championship in 2005 and 2006?",Answer: "Fernando Alonso",choiceA: "Paavo Nurmi",choiceB: "Fernando Alonso",choiceC: "Mark Spitz",choiceD: "Carl Lewis"},
  ],
	Difficult:[
		{Question:"From which country is the athlete Maria Mutola, who won her eighth world title in Paris in 2003?",Answer: "Mozambique",choiceA: "Turkmenistan",choiceB: "Pakistan",choiceC: "Dubai",choiceD: "Mozambique"},
		{Question:"Anna Kournikova won the doubles competition of the Australian Open of 1999. What swiss player was her partner?",Answer: "Martina Hingis",choiceA: "Mal Meninga",choiceB: "Mal Meningo",choiceC: "Martina Hingis",choiceD: "Martina Hingos"},
		{Question:"How many goals did Germany score in the 2014 World Cup Against Brazil?",Answer: "7",choiceA: "4",choiceB: "5",choiceC: "6",choiceD: "7"},
		{Question:"How many games were disputed in the longest match in the history of Wimbledon?",Answer: "183",choiceA: "183",choiceB: "184",choiceC: "185",choiceD: "186"},
		{Question:"Where were the first Pan American Games celebrated, in 1951?",Answer: "Buenos Aires",choiceA: "Canada",choiceB: "Kazakhstan",choiceC: "Buenos Aires",choiceD: "Argentina"},
  ]
  },
Entertainment:{
	Easy:[
		{Question:"Who played the character of Edward Scissorhands?",Answer: "Johnny Depp",choiceA: "Andrew Garfield",choiceB: "Johnny Depp",choiceC: "Morgan Freeman",choiceD: "Hugh Ackman"},
		{Question:	"The 2014 film Maleficent is based on which story?",Answer: "Sleeping Beauty",choiceA: "Snow White and The Seven Dwarves",choiceB: "Thumbelina",choiceC: "Sleeping Beauty",choiceD: "The Little Mermaid"},
		{Question:	"Who wrote the famous opera-rock song ‘ Bohemian Rhapsody’?",Answer: "Freddy Mercury",choiceA: "Paul Rogers",choiceB: "Freddy Mercury",choiceC: "Bryan Myers",choiceD: "Led Zeppelin"},
		{Question:	"Who was Naruto's first sensei?",Answer: "Iruka",choiceA: "Kakashi",choiceB: "Jiraya",choiceC: "Guy",choiceD: "Iruka"},{Question:"What color is the Little Mermaid's tail?",Answer: "Green",choiceA: "Violet",choiceB: "Green",choiceC: "Pink",choiceD: "Blue"}
	],
	Medium:[
		{Question:"What US president did Forrest Gump not meet?",Answer: "Eisenhower",choiceA: "Eisenhower",choiceB: "Washington",choiceC: "Johnson",choiceD: "Hoover"},
		{Question:	"With whom of the following was Michael Jackson married to?",Answer: "Lisa Marie Presley",choiceA: "Eliza Maria Presley",choiceB: "Lisa Marie Presley",choiceC: "Jira Angel",choiceD: "Dannah Esperanza"},
		{Question:	"What year did ‘Thriller’ come out?",Answer: "1982",choiceA: "1980",choiceB: "1981",choiceC: "1982",choiceD: "1983"},
		{Question:	"What year did the Red Hot Chili Peppers release their first album?",Answer: "1984",choiceA: "1984",choiceB: "1985",choiceC: "1986",choiceD: "1987"},
		{Question:	"What’s the name of the cat that wants to eat the smurfs?",Answer: "Azrael",choiceA: "Lux",choiceB: "Azrael",choiceC: "Ezikiel",choiceD: "Bob"}
	], 
	Difficult:[
		{Question:	"What was the address Dori was looking for on Finding Nemo?",Answer: "P Sherman 42 Wallaby Way Sidney",choiceA: "P Shermen 43 Wallaby Way Sidney",choiceB: "P Shermen 42 Wallaby Way Sidney",choiceC: "P Sherman 42 Wallaby Way Sidney",choiceD: "P Sherman 43 Wallaby Way Sidney"},
		{Question:	"How many letters did Noah write to Allie in The Notebook?",Answer: "365",choiceA: "361",choiceB: "363",choiceC: "365",choiceD: "367"},
		{Question:	"Who won the Academy Award for Best Actor in a Supporting Role in 2004?",Answer: "Morgan Freeman",choiceA: "Hugh Ackman",choiceB: "Morgan Freeman",choiceC: "Robert Downey Jr.",choiceD: "Jackie Chan"},
		{Question:	"What did Jack Nicholson play in the film ‘Prizzi’s Honour’?",Answer: "Mafia Hitman",choiceA: "Mafia Hitman",choiceB: "Information Broker",choiceC: "Boxer",choiceD: "Assasin"},
		{Question:	"Which actor portrayed Clark Kent in the movie ‘Man of Steel’?",Answer: "Henry Cavill",choiceA: "Dean Cain",choiceB: "Channing Tatum",choiceC: "Tim Daly",choiceD: "Henry Cavill"}
	]},
Science: {
	Easy:[
		{Question:"What does a glaucoma provoke if its not treated?",Answer: "Blindness",choiceA: "Deafness",choiceB: "Tremors",choiceC: "Nausea",choiceD: "Blindness"},
		{Question:	"Which two common household items have a violent chemical reaction when combined?",Answer: "Sodium bicarbonate and vinegar",choiceA: "Sodium bicarbonate and Ethanol",choiceB: "Vinegar and Sodium Hydroxide",choiceC: "Sodium bicarbonate and vinegar",choiceD: "Calcium carbonate and Sodium bicarbonate"},
		{Question:	"Au is an abbreviation for which chemical element?",Answer: "Gold",choiceA: "Gold",choiceB: "Silver",choiceC: "Copper",choiceD: "Iron"},			{Question:	"How is tooth cavity usually fixed?",Answer: "By filling it",choiceA: "By extracting it",choiceB: "By cleaning it",choiceC: "By replacing it with dentures",choiceD: "By filling it"},
		{Question:	"Which is the name of the most extended artery of the human body?",Answer: "Aorta",choiceA: "Aorta",choiceB: "Axilla",choiceC: "Arteria Dorsalis",choiceD: "Thoracic"}
		],
		Medium: [
		{Question:	"When are young elephants considered to be adults?",Answer: "12 to 15 years old",choiceA: "12 to 15 years old",choiceB: "13 to 16 years old",choiceC: "11 to 14 years old",choiceD: "10 to 13 years old"},
		{Question:	"Which part of the eye responds to light?",Answer: "Retina",choiceA: "Sclera",choiceB: "Cornea",choiceC: "Retina",choiceD: "Iris"},			{Question:	"What's the colostrum?",Answer: "The first breast milk",choiceA: "The first period",choiceB: "The first breast milk",choiceC: "The first pregnancy",choiceD: "The first ejaculation"},
		{Question:	"What is plastic made of?",Answer: "Oil",choiceA: "Leaves",choiceB: "Oil",choiceC: "Rocks",choiceD: "Wood"},
		{Question:	"What does vexillology study?",Answer: "Study of Flags",choiceA: "Study of Glands",choiceB: "Study of Worms",choiceC: "Study of Tides",choiceD: "Study of Flags"}
		],
	Difficult: [
		{Question:	"What's the name of the chronic mood disorder that alternates periods of hypomanic symptoms with periods of mild depression?",Answer: "Cyclothymia",choiceA: "Bipolar disorder",choiceB: "Major Depression",choiceC: "Cyclothymia",choiceD: "Dysthymia"},
		{Question:	"What prevents virus replication?",Answer: "Interferons",choiceA: "Algesia",choiceB: "Anodonta",choiceC: "Dorsalon",choiceD: "Interferons"},
		{Question:	"What does a speleologist study?",Answer: "Caves",choiceA: "Sun",choiceB: "Caves",choiceC: "Flags",choiceD: "Waves"},
		{Question:	"What is aboulia?",Answer: "A decrease of motivation",choiceA: "A decrease of emotion",choiceB: "A decrease of motivation",choiceC: "A sudden decrease of happiness",choiceD: "A decrease of energy"},
		{Question:	"The Statue of Liberty is covered in what material?",Answer: "Copper",choiceA: "Lead",choiceB: "Cadium",choiceC: "Copper",choiceD: "Scandium"}
		]
},
Geography:{
	Easy:[
		{Question:"What are the colors of the Philippines flag?",Answer:"Blue, Red, Yellow and White",choiceA:"Red and White",choiceB:"Red, White and Black",choiceC:"Blue, Red, Yellow and White",choiceD:"Red, Blue, and White"},
		{Question:"What country is famous for the maple tree?",Answer:"Canada",choiceA:"USA",choiceB:"UK",choiceC:"Philippines",choiceD:"Canada"},
		{Question:"What’s the meaning of D.C in Washington D.C?",Answer: "District of Columbia",choiceA:"District of Columbia",choiceB:"District of Cambodia",choiceC:"District of Canada",choiceD:"District of Caine"},
		{Question:"What is the color of the Japanese Flag?",Answer:"White and Red",choiceA:"Red and Yellow",choiceB: "White and Red",choiceC:"Red and Black",choiceD: "White and Black"},{Question:"When is the Spring in the Southern Hemisphere?",Answer:"September to December",choiceA:"December to March",choiceB:"March to June",choiceC:"June to September",choiceD:"September to December"}
	],
	Medium:[
		{Question:"Which of the following countries has the highest life expectancy?",Answer:"Japan",choiceA:"China",choiceB:"Japan",choiceC:"South Korea",choiceD:"North Korea"},
		{Question:"Where can you find the largest flower, Rafflesia?",Answer:"Malaysia",choiceA: "Indonesia",choiceB:"Singapore",choiceC:"Hong Kong",choiceD:"Malaysia"},
		{Question:"Taiwan is also known as?",Answer:"Formosa Island",choiceA:"Formosa Island",choiceB:"Fragrant Harbour",choiceC:"Spice Island",choiceD:"Insulinde"},
		{Question:"Which of the following countries does NOT have red in its flag?",Answer:"Saudi Arabia",choiceA:"China",choiceB:"Nepal",choiceC:"Saudi Arabia",choiceD:"Philippines"},
		{Question:"Which of these is NOT one of the ‘New Wonders of the World’?",Answer:"Eiffel Tower",choiceA:"Eiffel Tower",choiceB:"Christ the Redeemer Statue",choiceC:"Machu Picchu",choiceD:"Taj Majal"}
	], 
	Difficult:[
		{Question:"What country is the last to see the sun set?",Answer:"Samoa",choiceA:"Hawaii",choiceB:"New Zealand",choiceC:"Ecuador",choiceD:"Samoa"},
		{Question:"What element does Argentina owe its name to?",Answer:"Silver",choiceA:"Silver",choiceB:"Gold",choiceC:"Arsenic",choiceD:"Astatine"},
		{Question:"What is the real name of the Japanese Cat Island, famous for its huge cat population?",Answer:"Tashirojima",choiceA:"Inujima",choiceB:"Okunoshima",choiceC:"Tashirojima",choiceD:"Miyagi Zao"},
		{Question:"Where is the Capoeira dance from?",Answer: "Mafia Hitman",choiceA:"Brazil",choiceB:"Africa",choiceC:"India",choiceD:"Hawaii"},
		{Question:"Which is the most populated city of Turkey?",Answer:"Istanbul",choiceA:"Ankara",choiceB:"Izmir",choiceC:"Antalya",choiceD: "Istanbul"}
	]}, 
	History:{
	Easy:[
		{Question:"Who founded Playboy magazine?",Answer: "Hugh Hefner",choiceA: "Hugh Hefner",choiceB: "Henry Hudson",choiceC: "John Muir",choiceD: "Kit Carson"},
		{Question:"Who held the famous I have a dream speech in 1963?",Answer: "Martin Luther King",choiceA: "Abraham Lincoln",choiceB: "Thomas Jefferson",choiceC: "Martin Luther King",choiceD: "Franklin Roosevelt"},
		{Question:"Who was Britain’s longest-reigning monarch?",Answer: "Victoria",choiceA: "Anne",choiceB: "William",choiceC: "George",choiceD: "Victoria"},
		{Question:"Which was the weapon of choice for Samurais?",Answer: "Katana",choiceA: "Kama",choiceB: "Katana",choiceC: "Kiseru",choiceD: "Tekkan and Hachiwari"},
		{Question:"Who was the first president of the United States?",Answer: "George Washington",choiceA: "George Washington",choiceB: "Abraham Lincoln",choiceC: "George Bush",choiceD: "Theodore Roosevelt"},
  ],
	Medium:[
		{Question:"What was Sally Ride the first American woman to do?",Answer: "Go into outer space",choiceA: "Win an olympic medal",choiceB: "Go into outer space",choiceC: "Fly solo around the world.",choiceD: "Receive a pilot's license."},
		{Question:"What year did the Titanic sink?",Answer: "1912",choiceA: "1911",choiceB: "1910",choiceC: "1913",choiceD: "1912"},
		{Question:"What Wonder of the Ancient World was in what is Iraq today?",Answer: "Hanging gardens of Babylon",choiceA: "The Abbasid Palace",choiceB: "Ziggurat of Ur",choiceC: "Aqar Quf/ Dur-Kurigalzu",choiceD: "Hanging gardens of babylon"},
		{Question:"Where was Pearl Harbor, the military based attacked by the Japanese army was located?",Answer: "Hawaii",choiceA: "Israel",choiceB: "Philippines",choiceC: "Hawaii",choiceD: "America"},
		{Question:"What starts with ‘Four score and seven years ago?",Answer: "Gettsburg Address",choiceA: "Gettsburg Address",choiceB: "We Shall Fight on the Beaches",choiceC: "Surrender Speech",choiceD: "Farewell to Baseball Address"},
  ],
	Difficult:[
		{Question:"What country did USA purchase Alaska from?",Answer: "Russia",choiceA: "Cuba",choiceB: "Russia",choiceC: "Argentina",choiceD: "Venezuela"},
		{Question:"What was one of the names given to the atomic bombs of Hiroshima and Nagasaki?",Answer: "Little Boy",choiceA: "Little Boy",choiceB: "Little Man",choiceC: "Little Guy",choiceD: "Fat Boy"},
		{Question:"Who discovered the sea route to India?",Answer: "Vasco Da Gama",choiceA: "Narendra Modi",choiceB: "Vasco Da Gama",choiceC: "Aamir Khan",choiceD: "Virat Kohli"},
		{Question:"What was the name of Adolf Hitler’s wife?",Answer: "Eva",choiceA: "Evie",choiceB: "Eve",choiceC: "Evelyn",choiceD: "Eva"},
		{Question:"The Philippines was discovered by Europeans in what year?",Answer: "1521",choiceA: "1521",choiceB: "1522",choiceC: "1523",choiceD: "1524"},
  ]
  }
}])